{
    "subject": "resource/Miss_USA_1990",
    "predicate": "property/presenters",
    "object": "Dick Clark, Leeza Gibbons and Laura Harring",
    "human_readable": "The presenters of Miss USA 1990 were Dick Clark, Leeza Gibbons and Laura Harring.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9527157545089722,
            "question": "Who were the presenters of Miss USA 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9524544477462769,
            "question": "Did Leeza Gibbons present Miss USA in 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9413121938705444,
            "question": "Name one of the presenters of Miss USA 1990."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9308874011039734,
            "question": "Who presented alongside Dick Clark at Miss USA 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.929615318775177,
            "question": "Was Laura Harring involved in the Miss USA pageant of 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9015802145004272,
            "question": "What was Laura Harring's role in the Miss USA pageant of 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7626764178276062,
            "question": "What year did Dick Clark present Miss USA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697953939437866,
            "question": "Can you list all three presenters of Miss USA 1990?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5463755130767822,
            "question": "What other events might Leeza Gibbons have presented?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47200027108192444,
            "question": "Apart from presenting, what else is Dick Clark known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The presenters of Miss USA 1990 were Dick Clark, Leeza Gibbons and Laura Harring.",
            "html": "dbpedia_816_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other events might Leeza Gibbons have presented?",
            "html": "dbpedia_816_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you list all three presenters of Miss USA 1990?",
            "html": "dbpedia_816_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Dick Clark present Miss USA?",
            "html": "dbpedia_816_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_816_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that the presenters for the 1990 Miss USA pageant included Dick Clark, Leeza Gibbons, and Laura Harring."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}